# Sébastien André Bagdasarianz

Address: Hausackerstrasse 8, 8916 Jonen AG

Phone: +41 78 800 87 63

E-Mail: <u>sebbagdasarianz@gmail.com</u>
Date of Birth: <u>o8. March 2001 in Geneva</u>

Nationalities: Switzerland (Father) und Colombia (Mother)

Profile:

Social: Fluent in 4 languages

Engagement: Team spirit in work and sport, goal-oriented

Motivation: - Developed and programmed a robot using Arduino for my Matura thesis.

- Strong interest in software development and data science.

- Accumulated two years of dedicated Practice in Java, focusing on

algorithms and data structures.

## **Education:**

09.2022 – Today: Data Science Studies at University of Applied Sciences and Arts

Northwestern Switzerland (FHNW)

10.2022 – 06.2024: Computer Science Studies at ETH Zurich 10.2021 – 06.2022: Electrical Engineering Studies at ETH Zurich

2014 – 2020: Swiss Matura, Focus: Mathematics and Physics at Freies Gymnasium Zürich

#### Experience:

06.2022 – 10.2022: Vacation temp, Coop Stauffacher

Assisted customers and managed inventoryEnhanced communication and teamwork skills

01.2021 - 10.2021: Military service: "Rekrutenschule und Unteroffiziersschule"

- Grade: Sergeant, Function: Scouts / Sniper

- Developed leadership skills and ability to work under pressure

### Language Skills:

German: Fluent - Mother tongue like Swiss German: Fluent - Mother tongue like

French: Mother tongue Spanish: Mother tongue

English: Fluent - Cambridge Certificate in Advanced English (C1)

### Document editing / Programming:

- Python – Intermediate Level

- R – Intermediate Level

- Java – Intermediate Level

- HTML & CSS – Intermediate Level

- TeX / LaTeX Editor – Intermediate Level

- C++ – Basics

#### **Hobbies and Interests:**

Sport: Brazilian Jiu-Jitsu, Football, Snow sports, Chess, Drums Interests: Culture, History, Computer Science, Technology, Music

